Guide to the Ernest J. Sternglass papers, [ca. 1952-2008]
Sternglass, Ernest J. papers
- Alphabetical File List
  - Cancer Mortality Maps, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Cancer Mechanisms and Relevance to Sr90, 1982-2007 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Cancer Mortality >65. Closing and Start. (Jay Gould's Graphs), 2000 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Cancer Prevention Coalition, 1994-1997 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Cancer Prevention. Vitamins A, E, C and Dietary Anti-Oxydants, 1987-1994 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Cancer of Prostate, 1991-2000 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Cancer Rates, Recent Trends (1973-1988). Inconsistent With Smoking, Male and Female, Age, 1986-1998 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Cancer: Role of Chemicals. Natural and Synthetic Compared: Relation to Our Fission Product Findings, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Cancer, Skin - Melanoma, 1980-1999 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Cancer Statistics. Europe, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Cancer Therapies. Gene and Antibody Use, 1981-2000 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Cancer Treatment - New, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Cape Cod Pilgrim Cancer Epidemy, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Carlyle Group. Weapons Manufacturing, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Cassini Protest (E-mails and Website) October 1997, 1997-1999 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Cassini Trial Testimony. December 1997 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Cattle Disease and Fallouts, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - C-14 Contamination of Environment by Bomb Tests and Reactors, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Chart Blanks. Infant Mortality and a US Map (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Chelyabinsk. Disasters in USSR, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Chernobyl - 1992 ->, 1992-1996 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Chernobyl Contamination (Medvedev, Z. A. Articla), 1987 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Chernobyl. Ernest J. Sternglass. 5th Anniversary Talk at UN, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Chernobyl. Implications for Human Health, 1986-2006 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Chernobyl Paper. Ran Data Used by Jay for Munster (10% Sample) (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Chernobyl. Radiation Contamination, 1986-2001 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Chernobyl. Toronto 1988 Paper (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Chernousenko Correspondence (7-16-1993), 1992 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Chernousenko, Vladimir (Visit to NY, October 1993) (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Chesapeake Bay Polution (Possible Relation to Nuclear Releases), 1977 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Childhood Cancer Epidemics - 2000 (Icluding Joe Mangano's Papers), 1999-2006 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Children's Defense Fund, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Chinese Fallout 1976. Infant Mortality in US (July 18, 1977 Paper Presented at US Academy of Science), 1997 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Christic Institute (Silkwood Case) (Rob Hager), 1987 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Chromosome Damage. Radiation, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Chronic Fatigue Syndrome, 1987-1999 (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Chronic Fatigue Syndrome (Joe Manfand), 1991 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Citizens for Health, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Claims on Exposure. Atomic Veterans National Association, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Climate and Other Environmental Effects of Fission Products, 1995-2003 (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Clinton, Bill. Economy Problems. Health Costs, etc., 1993 (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Clinton, Hillary, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Coalition for Nuclear Disarmament (Gail Colby), 1992 (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - Cobb, S, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - Competitiveness of US and Fallout, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 79)
  - Computer and Communication Related Materials, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - Computers (Box 19, Folder 81)
  - Computers and E-mail. Communication Revolution, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 82)
  - Computer Use - E-mail, Web, 1998-2002 (Box 19, Folder 83)
  - Congenital Defects Incidence, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 84)
  - Congenital Defects and Vitamins, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 85)
  - Connecticut Cancer Changes, 1977-1981 (Box 19, Folder 86)
  - Connecticut Environmental Organizations (Lecture at Gail Merrill's Home 10/26/2002) (Box 19, Folder 87)
  - Copenhagen Lectures - 1996 London (Box 19, Folder 88)
  - Council on Economic Priorities (CEP) Jay Gould, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 89)
  - Crib Death, 1972-1983 (Box 19, Folder 90)
  - Crime and Fallout. Homicide and Other Crimes, 1979-2005 (Box 19, Folder 91)
  - Crime and Fallout. Multiple Murders (Box 19, Folder 92)
  - Crime Rate and Fallout Damage. Child Abuse, Drug Use, Suicide, Violence, 1984-2002 (Box 19, Folder 93)
  - Critical Mass Energy Project (Public Citizen), 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 94)
  - Curry, Bill. Article and Miscellaneous. April 14, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 95)
  - Danny's Proposal, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 96)
  - Depleted Uranium, 1991-2004 (Box 19, Folder 97)
  - Darwin, Charles, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 98)
  - DeGroot, Morris, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 99)
  - Department of Energy Plants Problems 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 100)
  - Determinism. Hyder, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 101)
  - Detroit. Air Pollution, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 102)
  - Detroit. Fermi Data, Graphs, and Report, 1998-2000 (Box 19, Folder 103)
  - De Vaucouleurs, G., 1992-1996 (Box 19, Folder 104)
  - Diet, Fallout and Health. High Blood Pressure, etc., 1969-1989 (Box 19, Folder 105)
  - Dietician's Notes (1/1997) (Box 19, Folder 106)
  - Diet, Sr90. Diffusion Foods, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 107)
  - Dioxin, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 108)
  - Disability Rise, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 109)
  - Dolphin Deaths (1987) (Box 19, Folder 110)
  - Dose Factors (Box 19, Folder 111)
  - Downs Syndrome, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 112)
  - Downwinders Trial - Utah. Judge Bruce Jenkins - Howard Ball (Box 19, Folder 113)
  - Drug Abuse, Anxiety and Fallout. Brain Chemistry Damage, 1980-1996 (Box 19, Folder 114)
  - Drugs and Fallout (D.C. as Example). Biological Basis: Too Little Dopamine, 1989-1999 (Box 19, Folder 115)
  - Duesberg, P (1990-1991) (Box 19, Folder 116)
  - Dyslexia, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 117)
  - Dyson, F, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 118)
  - Earth Day - 1990 Plans (Box 19, Folder 119)
  - Economic Failure of Nuclear Power. Komanoff (Box 19, Folder 120)
  - Electromagnetic Field Effects on Health, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 121)
  - APS News, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 122)
  - Energy Plan Battle - Bush (5-16-2001) (Box 19, Folder 123)
  - Energy Sources and Taxes, 1993-2005 (Box 19, Folder 124)
  - Environmental Coalition (2002) (Box 19, Folder 125)
  - Environmental and Consumer Coalition - NY 1989, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 126)
  - Environmental Health: Government Cover and Politics. Blaming Chemicals, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 127)
  - Environmental Health Research Plans for East Block, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 128)
  - Environmental Policy and Organizations, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 129)
  - Environmental Protection Agency Data Falsification, 1986-1993 (Box 19, Folder 130)
  - Environmental Protection Agency. Drinking Water Brochure. Run-off Enforcement, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 131)
  - Environmental Protection Agency. Letter to Richardson, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 132)
  - Environmental Protection Agency. Milk Data Falsification Draft, 1984-1990 (Box 19, Folder 133)
  - Environmental Protection Agency. Milk Falsification Plots (To Cover Up the 1982 Pilgrim Accident), 1985 (Box 19, Folder 134)
  - Environmental Protection Agency. Radiation Related Publications 1973-1987 (Nuclear Plant Related) (Box 19, Folder 135)
  - Environmental Protection Agency Research, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 136)
  - Environmental Regulation and Laws, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Enviro-Video. Steve Jambeck, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Epilepsy, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Epstein, Sam S. Articles, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Ernst J Sternglass. Intoduction to Sara Shanon's 1993 Revised "Diet for the Atomic Age" (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Ernst J Sternglass and Jay M Gould. "Health Effects of Underground Testing.", 1993 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Evolution - Human, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Fallout and Abortion, 1974-1999 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Fallout and Asthma, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Fallout and Climate, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Fallout and Diet: Uptake of Cs-137 By Fruit Trees and Diet Differences (Racial), 1993-2001 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Fallout, Divorce, Violence and Juvenile Crime, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Fallout and Economic Impact (1995-1996). Health Care Costs, 1991-2007 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Fallout: Economic Impact. US Banks I, 1977-2000 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Fallout: Economic Impact. US Banks II, 1977-2000 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Fallout and Ectoric Pregnancies, 1983-1994 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Fallout. Effects on Alcohol and Drug Use, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Fallout, Effects on Fetus. Alcohol and Drug Addictions, etc., 1995-2001 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Fallout Effects on Social and Political Life, 1995-1999 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Fallout and Fertility (China), 1991 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Fallout abd Fertility: Increased Births, Decreased Sperm Count. 1995 Abnormal Pregnancy Rise, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Fallout and High School and College Graduation, 1994-1999 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Fallout and Life Expectancy. Diseases (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Fallout and Maternal Mortality, Black 1999, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Fallout and Mentall Illness and Hyper Activity, 1986-1999 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Fallout and Mutation of Microorganisms, 1993-1999 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Fallout and Political Impact (1994), 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Fallout and Rampage Killings, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Fallout and Rise of Violence - 1995. Oklahoma City Bombing. Abuse, Children Fleeing Home, 1994-1999 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Fallout and Run-Off, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Fallout and Social Well Being. Bomb and Nuclear Plant Effects on Society. Corruption and White Collar Crime. Sexual Orientation and Behavior. etc., 2001-2007 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Fallout and Suicide (D.C. Cole), 1988 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Fallout and Teen Pregnancies and Sexual Activity at Earlier Age, 1998-2000 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Fallout and Violence. Mental Illness (For Adults and Children), 2001 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Falsification of Birth and IMR data. Chernobyl and Three Mile Island and Pilgrim (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Federation of American Scientists. Council Members 1993 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Fermi - Br, Ca, etc. (1994 Study), 1995-1998 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Fermi II Affidavit - 1997 Data, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Fertility and Fallout, 1986-1995 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Fertility and Fallout. Radioactivity and Decreased Fertility (Life Births Change After Bravo), 1998 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Fish. Effects of Fallout on. Also Whales, Coral Reefs, etc., 1971-2005 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Fish Oil and Health, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Florida Cancer Mortality vs. San Francisco (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Fluoride and Radiation Toxicity., 1983-1998 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Food Additives Regulation 1987 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Food Irradiation, 1968-1986 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Food Irradiation, Hazards, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - "Food and Water" (Food Irradiation)(Wally Burnstein's), 1994 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Foot and Mouth Disease Epidemics 2001 United Kingdom, Europe (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Forest Damage and Nuclear Releases of O2-, 1985-1998 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Forest Damage, Radiation, 1970-2001 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Franke, Bernd, 1980-1986 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Franke, Richard, 1992-2001 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Fraud and Falsification in Science (1988). Recent Concerns (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Free Radical O2- (Petkau). Effects on Immune System, 1975-1996 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Free Radicals and Disease, 1974-2000 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - French Nuclear Tests, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Frog and Amphibians Decline and Fallout, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Frontier Sciences Center, Philadelphia (1990-1991) (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Fuel Cells. High Efficiency, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Gagner Letter on Radiation Biological Hazard, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Galileo Misson Testimony, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - General Electrics Reactors. Boiling Water Reactors. Iternational Memo on Large Releases, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Genes and Behavior (Fallout Effects During Intra-Utero Development. Not Considerable), 1994 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Genome Project, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Gervsky Affair, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Gofman, John, 1979-1996 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Gofman, J. Analysis of Hiroshima Data, 1993-2003 (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Goodman, Leo, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Gould, Jay. Draft., 1998 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Gould, Jay. Graphs on Radiation Effects, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Gould, J (Book Draft 1989) (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Gould, J. Connecticut Breast and Thyroid Cancer (1995). Presentaton of Jay Gould (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Gould, J.M. Articles, 1993-1998 (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Gould, J.M. 1995 Berlin Paper. Nuclear Reactors Draft, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - Gould, J.M. Breast Cancer Maps (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Gould, J.M. "Earth Summit" 1992, 1983-1994 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - Gould, J. Miscellaneous Talks and Drafts, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - Gould, J.M. 1996 New York Metropolitan Pamphlet (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - Gould, J.M. Westchester Talk, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - Gould, J. Prostate Cancer (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - Gould's Data Base Printout for Reactor Study By County (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - Grossman, Karl, 1996-1999 (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - Grunbaum, A, 1983-1990 (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - Hanford Downwinder Littigation. Tom Foulds, 1991-1994 (Box 20, Folder 85)
  - Hanford (Heal), 1986 (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Hanford Health Information Network, 1986-1995 (Box 20, Folder 87)
  - Hanford 1986 Health Study (9/86). Planning Meeting (Box 20, Folder 88)
  - Hanford Plant Problems, 1985-1996 (Box 20, Folder 89)
  - Hanford Purex Accident and Trial, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 90)
  - Hanford Radiation Study 1990. Tom H Foulds, Esq., Seattle, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 91)
  - Hartsville Test, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 92)
  - Harvard Involvement With NRC, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 93)
  - Hatch Paper on Three Mile Island, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 94)
  - Heal. Organization and Talk, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 95)
  - Health Care. Clinton Problems and Plans, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 96)
  - Health Care Cost Spiral and Radiation, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 97)
  - Health Effects of Nuclear Power 1990-1991, 1990-2008 (Box 20, Folder 98)
  - Health Effects. Underground Test 1993 (Box 20, Folder 99)
  - Health and Energy Institute. Commission on Prenatal and Child Health, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 100)
  - Health, Personal, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 101)
  - Health (Personal). Cholesterol and HDL, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 102)
  - Health; Risk Analysis; public. Cancer Causes. Science Community and Media, 1988-1992 (Box 20, Folder 103)
  - Health and Wealfare. Cost Rise (Memo). Ending Rapid Rise - Phase out Nukes, 1990-1993 (Box 20, Folder 104)
  - Hearing Loss and Radiation (Eskimos), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 105)
  - Heart Disease and Fallout. Arteries and Virus. Immune System Damage, 1985-2005 (Box 20, Folder 106)
  - Hiroshima - Nagasaki Reanalysis, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 107)
  - Hofstadter, Robert, 1975-1992 (Box 20, Folder 108)
  - Homeopathy. Case History (Dr. Christoph Thomas), 1991-1995 (Box 20, Folder 109)
  - Homicide Rise '70-'79 (LA), 1986 (Box 20, Folder 110)
  - Homosexuality. Biological Origin. Hormonal Distribution. Tests, 1984-2007 (Box 20, Folder 111)
  - Homosexuality. Biological Origin. Related to AIDS. Birth Damage, 1991-1993 (Box 20, Folder 112)
  - Honicker, Jeanine, 1995-2002 (Box 20, Folder 113)
  - Hooper, Ed, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 114)
  - Hormesis, 1987-1989 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Hormesis. Beneficial Aspects of Radiation, 1982-1991 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Human Experiments. AEC, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Human Radiation Experiments. Testimony March 15, 1995, 1976-1994 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Hypothyroidism, Infants (Mangano's Data and Papers). [5 Inch Diskette], 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - I-131 in Diet, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - I-131 Doses ad Effects, 1962-1980 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - I-131 and Hypothyroid and Fetal Effects. Three Mile Island Data, 1964-1980 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - I-131 in Milk. US 1980s, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Iakimets, Vladimir (See Also Graeub File for Correspondence), 1992 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Iceland Summit, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Immune Damage (For Berlin 1992). Mutation of Viruses, 1975-1999 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Immune System and Cancer, 1978-1995 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Immune System Damage. Epidemic Environment and Infectious Diseases, 1988-2001 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Immune System, Fallout and Infant Diseases, 1982-1993 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Immune System and Interaction With Gonadal System, 1986-2007 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Immune System and Nuclear Fallout. AIDS. Polio Peaks and Other Infectious Diseases, 1975-1996 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Incineration. Health Effects of Air Pollution, 1967-1995 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Incinerator. Rockefeller. Manhattan. Battle to Stop It, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Indian Point (Includes Water Supply For New York), 1986-2007 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Indian Point 1992 Radiation Release, 1990-1992 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Indian Point 1991 Study (Jay's Data Base), 1982-1995 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Infant Leukemia and Alcohol, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Infant Mortality After Chernobyl in Kiev and Bavaria, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Infant Mortality Change 1983-1984, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Infant Mortality (Children's Defense Fund Report Outline) (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Infant Mortality by City, State, 1985-2000 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Infant Mortality at Hiroshima. Kato, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Infant Mortality and Low Bith Weight, 1980-1985 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Infant Mortality In Minnes (Monticello Reactor), 1980 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Infant Mortality. New England. 1968-1980 Bar Graphs (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Infant Mortality in New Jersey (PDA) (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Infant Mortality and Nuclear Power. Illinois Vs. New Hampshire (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Infant Mortality. Premature. Sr-90. Biological Mechanisms. Reproduction and Immune System, 1970-1990 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Infant Mortality Rates. Yearly Mortality By State (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Infant Mortality 1988 Report. National Commission (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Infant Mortality Rise. Trinity. First Evidence of Rapid Effects on Fetus, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Infant Mortality in US. By Cause, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Infant Mortality in US (Pittsburgh Print-Outs), 1988-2001 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Infant Mortality. 35-85 US States. Copies of Graphs (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Infants At Risk Report (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Infectious Disease. Evolution of Virulence, 1992-1995 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Inglis and Hoffman. Review of Low Level Radiation, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Institute for Energy and Environmental Research. Arjun Makhijani, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Institute for Policy Studies, 1986-1988 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - International Physicians for the Prevention of Nuclear War, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Introduction to 2nd Edition "Diet For Atomic Age," By Sara Shannon (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Investment Ideas - 1990, 1990-1996 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Investment Information 1991, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Iodine - Thyroid Dose and Damage, 1961-1990 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Iowa Test Scores and Fallout, 1991-2001 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Iron And Heart Disease. Radiation, 1971-1992 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Japan. Hotels, Travel Ideas, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Japanese Anti-Nuclear Activist Nakagawa, 1985-1987 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Japanese plutonium Danger and Kr-85, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Johnson, Carl I, 1977-2002 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Johnson, Carl II, 1977-2002 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Johnsrud, Judy, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Khazakstan Nuclear Test Exposures, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Kelly, Petra, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Kennedy, J.F. (Nuclear War), 1993 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Khrushchev and Arms Control, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Kiick Case (Three Mile Island), 1986 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Lavel, L, etc. Low Level Radiation and US Mortality, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Lead-210, Bone and Soft Organ Redistribution, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Lead Toxicity (Needleman), 1979-2000 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Learning Disability, Brain Damage, Immune Defficiency, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Learning Disabilities - Fallout Related, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Lederberg, J, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Legal Aspects of Low Level Raiation Injury. Kanner (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Legal Case (1987) Lopez, Virginia, 1984-1987 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Leukemia Around Nuclear Plants. Germany and United Kingdom, 1988-1994 (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Leukemia. Immune System Damage, 1957-1999 (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Leukemia Near Sellafield, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Leukemia X-Ray Experiment, 1961-1979 (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Life Expectancy (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - London. April 24, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Longevity Research Journal. 1994 Article (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Lung Cancer, 1986-1998 (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Lung Disease. Lung Association, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - Lyme Disease and Nuclear Releases, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Macleod, Gordon, 1979-1985 (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - Mad Cow Disease and Fallout from Chernobyl, 1996-2001 (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Maine Yankee Study, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Mangano. Infant Leukemia After Chernobyl, 1994-1999 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Mangano, J. Connecticut Health Change, 1996-1998 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Mangano, J. Hypothyroid and I-131 Data and Article Drafts, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Mangano, Joe, 1991-2000 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Mangano, Joe, 1994-2000 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Mangano Slides for Berlin, 1995-1997 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Maxwell, Nicholas (Philosophy of Science), 1992-1994 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - McGraw Hill Contract, 1986-1989 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Medvedev, Z.A. (Chernobyl Contamination), 1987 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Membrane, Radiation Effects on. Lund; O2- Free Radiacal, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Memory, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Meno, Frank, 1991-1999 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Methodists United. 1996 Conference (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Michigan. Leukemia and Nuclear Releases, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Mighty Oak Fallout in Canada, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Milk Purity Battle. Hormones and Radiation (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Millpointer, Kate, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Mineapolis, MN. Press Conference. Breast Cancer. Prairie Island, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Minnesota 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Moeller, Dode (HPS Statement), 1971 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report (MMWR) Articles Related to Fallout Effects, 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Moret, Leorn, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Morgan, K.Z., 1977-1999 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Morrison, Philip. History of Atomic Age, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Mortality and Life Expectany, 1974-2001 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Moshkevich, Viktor, 1991-1994 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Motz, Lloyo, 1970-1992 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Muenster Symposium-Papers, 1988-1998 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Multiple Murders. New York Times. April 9, 2000 Article (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Multiple Myeloma. NCI Wing, US, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Nakagawa, Yasuo and Keiko (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - National Association for Public Health Policy, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - National Cancer Institute, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Natural Killer Cells, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Naturopathic Physicians. Teaching, 1993-1995 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Nevada and Downwind States. 1968-1980. Effects of Underground Tests on Infant Mortality (Summer), 1986 (Box 22, Folder 37)